你的救命恩人
Your salvation.
驾 驾
Hyah, hyah!
我觉得我们之前没见过
I don't believe we've ever met.
不 我们没有
No, we haven't.
你总是像一种
You know, you always seemed like a--
一种市场测试之类的东西
a market-tested kind of thing.
大名鼎鼎 伤疤别致
Big gun, tasteful scar.
却被锁在狭小范围内
Locked in your little cycle
像一只珍贵的贵宾犬咬自己的尾巴
like a prized poodle after its own tail.
你听起来像是一个对满腹胆识
You sound like a man who's grown tired
感到厌倦的男人
of wearing his guts on the inside.
没必要再试探了
There's no need to get testy.
我只是对你的世界观表示好奇
I'm just curious about your worldview.
是某种半本土化的胡言乱语吗
Some kind of half-native mumbo jumbo?
很简单
It's simple.
我相信只有真正勇敢的人
I believe that only the truly brave
才可以审视这世界并且理解
can look at the world and understand
全部
that all of it--
神 人
gods, men,
以及其他所有的人 都会以悲剧收场
everything else-- will end badly.
无人得救
No one will be saved.
也许我们比我想的有更多的共同点
Maybe we've got more in common than I thought.
你呢
What about you?
什么风把你吹到这里
What turns of fate have brought you here?
说来话长
It's a long story.
而且我们没时间了
And we don't have the time.
可惜 你比你的朋友有更多的时间
Got more time than your friend, sadly.
我朋友出现之前还有几天时间
It will be a few more days before my friends show up.
三天
Three days.
正常情况下
Normally.
我怕我没有时间等
I'm afraid I don't have time for that,
我们现在就走
so we're leaving now.
我收到一个需要烟火效应的请求
I've got a request for a pyrotechnic effect.
Los Diablos 低利息 分两次收费
Los Diablos, low-yield, two charges.
Los Diablos是一张由委内瑞拉作曲家Aldemaro Romero作曲的33转黑胶唱片，由唱片公司Cymbal发行于1962年，。
同意
Approved.
批准
Authorizing.
动起来  Hector
Step lively, Hector.
你还有什么遗言吗
Any last words?
别废话 快动手
Get it over with.
啊
Yah!
操你妈
Motherfucker.
一局制胜
One match.
你是一个能干的人
You're a capable man.
要去的那个地方我们能帮得上忙吗
We could do with your help where we're going.
恐怕不能
Afraid not.
我们欠你一份人情
We owe you a debt.
不 你朋友只欠
No, your friend here
我一个承诺或两个
simply owes me a word or two.
这就行了
That'll do.
和一个
And a word of advice--
你要找的那个东西的建议
that thing you're looking for?
你永远不会在那个保险柜里找到它
You're never gonna find it in that safe.
我七岁时 他们来到我的城镇
I was seven when they rode into my town.
戴着面具 有着魔鬼的角
Masked men in devils' horns.
他们杀了所有人
They killed everyone--
妇女 孩童 甚至那些动物
women, children, even the animals.
他们把我母亲从上到下糟蹋了一遍
They gutted my mother from her jaw to her sex.
我不得不把她的血
I had to paint her warm blood
涂在我身上
over my skin to make sure
好让他们以为我已经死了
that they would think I was dead.
我追踪他们每一个人
Every one of them I tracked down,
我再一次在我身上涂上他们的血
I used their blood to paint my skin again.
只有一个人活着
Only one man left.
蛇首
The head of the snake.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
他有很多名字
He has many names.
大部分人都叫他Wyatt
Most know him as Wyatt.
嘿 小姑娘 这 这是什么
Hey, little girl, what-- what is this?
这是什么意思
What does it mean?
不要浪费你的力气 女士
Don't waste your breath, lady.
这东西是他们所谓的宗教的一部分
That thing's part of their so-called religion.
他们一个字也不会跟你说的
Ain't none of them's gonna tell you nothing about that.
一小时5刀
It's $5 for an hour,
你先洗澡的话4刀
4 if you bathe first.
如果我们只要一个
Well, if we just get the one,
第二次和接下来能打折吗
do I get a discount for being second and all?
我相信我们能合作愉快
I'm sure we can work something out.
来吧
Come on.
那个高个子 我之前见过他
The tall one, I've seen him before,
在邮局的窗口那晃荡
hanging in the window of the post office.
土匪
Bandits?
你认为他们在这里是为了什么
Do you think they're here for something?
比起Franny的正面 我认为他们
I think they're interested in more than a turn
对这感兴趣
at Franny's backside.
我想他和Hector是同行的
I think he rides with Hector.
那个人是他们说的与野人一起生活的人吗
Is that the one they say lives out with the savages?
就是他
That's the one.
就要走了 我才刚到这
Taking off? I just got here.
我要什么你已经给了
You gave me what I needed.
这就是我擅长的吗
So, is that all I'm good for?
- 释放一点压力  - 谁说我有压力
- Letting off a little stress? - Who says I'm stressed?
你说的
You have your tells.
是 Bernard
Oh, yes, Bernard,
观察家
master of observation.
明天我要跟Ford谈一谈
Tomorrow I have to talk to Ford.
- 为什么  - 他在乐园里制造混乱
- Why? - He's creating chaos in the park.
而董事会随时会降责
And the board will be descending at any moment.
我需要再来点时间
I need to buy some time.
有任何建议吗
Some advice?
最好不要告诉他你很紧张或有所防备
Best to not show him you're nervous or defensive.
我没什么可防备的
I have nothing to be defensive about.
那就不要把你的手臂交叉起来
Then don't cross your arms.
这是一个古老的本能
It's an ancient instinct.
腹部是每个生物最脆弱的部分
The belly is the most vulnerable part of every animal.
把我跟与一个凶残的野兽做比较 听起来很性感
It's so sexy being compared to a frightened beast.
Ah.
看
There.
这才是你要做的姿势
That's the posture you're looking for.
有时候
Sometimes,
只要你竭尽全力
despite your best efforts,
你就真的很迷人了
you can actually be quite charming.
邻居有抱怨过吗
Have the neighbors complained?
只是说 他们只是问些问题
Safe to say, they're asking questions.
最好还是不要动这些石头
The rocks would prefer not to move,
但是我们就是要动
but we shall move them yet.
也许我能帮你
Perhaps I can help you with that.
你创造的故事线
The narrative you're creating
显然花费的努力巨大
is clearly a massive endeavor.
如果你需要更多的时间 我相信董事会
If you need more time, I'm sure the board
更乐意效劳
would be happy to oblige.
我相信他们更会乐意
I'm sure they'd be happier
无限地为我延期
for me to delay it indefinitely.
跟我来
Come with me.
你以为我会生气
You imagine I have gone mad...
对吗
do you?
会迷失方向
Lost my way?
我们只是关心
We're simply concerned
你做出改变的内容
about the extent of the changes you're making.
我们想要保护你的遗产
We want to protect your legacy.
我的遗产
My legacy?
你们其实并不是很喜欢这个地方 是不是
You don't like this place very much, do you?
这几年我看到你们进进出出很多次
I've seen many of you come and go over the years,
我能说出来谁是乐在其中的
and I can tell the ones who enjoy their time here
谁不是
and the ones who don't.
我羡慕它
I admire it,
羡慕它的大胆无畏
the audacity of it.
- 噢  - 我差点忘了它是有多美丽
- Oh. - I've forgotten how beautiful it is.
当我还是个孩子的时候和父母来过这儿一次
I came here once as a child with my parents.
我觉得我甚至就坐在这张桌子上
I think we even sat at this table.
又或者 是那张
Or maybe-- maybe that one.
当我开始在这工作的时候
When I started working here,
我意识到这地方并不是我热衷的地方
I realized this place wasn't something I would enjoy.
恩
Ah.
一开始 我设想所有的东西都是
In the beginning, I imagined things would be
完美地平衡的
perfectly balanced.
甚至跟我搭档Arnold对它的效果打赌
Even had a bet with my partner, Arnold, to that effect.
我们做了一百个有希望的故事情节
We made a hundred hopeful storylines.
当然 几乎没有人赞同我们的故事
Of course, almost no one took us up on them.
我输了那个赌约
I lost the bet.
Anold总是揪出一个人的阴暗面
Arnold always held a somewhat dim view of people.
他更偏爱主人
He preferred the hosts.
他打赌我不会让你们参与进来
He begged me to not let you people in,
商人
the moneymen.
Delos.
但是我告诉他我们是可以的
But I told him we'd be fine,
你们不会明白是在为什么付钱
that you didn't understand what you were paying for.
这不是一个商业投资 不是一个主题公园
It's not a business venture, not a theme park,
而是整个世界
but an entire world.
我们设计了它的每一方每一寸
We designed every inch of it.
每片草的叶子
Every blade of grass.
在这里 我们就是神
In here, we were gods.
但你们仅仅是我们的客人
And you were merely our guests.
但是这对Arnold怎么可行
And how did that work out for Arnold?
可惜 他失去了理智
Sadly, he lost his perspective.
他疯了
He went mad.
而我没有 你们都知道
I haven't, as you well know.
我总是对事情
I have always seen things
明查洞悉
very clearly.
这就是我和我父母之前坐的桌子
This is the table I sat at with my parents.
这是我坐的椅子
This is the chair I sat in.
我们知道客人的一切信息 不是吗
We know everything about our guests, don't we?
就像我们知道员工的一切信息
As we know everything about our employees.
我希望你能小心Bernard一点
I do hope you will be careful with Bernard.
他很敏感
He has a sensitive disposition.
请再说一遍 小姐
I beg your pardon, señorita.
这些年来像你这样的人有很多
There have been many of you over the years,
而我们总是 差不多总是
and we have always-- almost always
找到说服你们的方式
found a way to make it work.
我好好的跟你说
So, I will ask you nicely,
请
please...
不要挡我的路
don't get in my way.
董事会会同意我的观点
The board will agree with me.
他们会派代表来
They'll be sending a representative.
他们已经派来了
But they already have.
我认为他们会跟你说
I thought they would've told you.
还需要菜单吗
That won't be necessary, Manu.
不需要
Not anymore.
你可以忙别的了
You can join the others.
你可以告诉董事会我的故事线
You can tell the board that my narrative
会按时完成的
will be completed on time,